let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Programs in c# are contained in a _____",
        answer: "type definition",
        options: [
          "class only",
          "interface",
          "type definition",
          "objects"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "in c# it is ______ to create global functioin",
        answer: "not possible",
        options: [
          "possible",
          "not possible",
          "some times possible",
          "none of the above"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "UDT stands for what ?",
        answer: "user defined type ",
        options: [
          "user defined type ",
          "unorganised data type",
          "united data types",
          "user definition types"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "we can define class members as static by using _______ keyword",
        answer: "static",
        options: [
          "non static",
          "dynamic",
          "static",
          "ststics"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "CLR stands for",
        answer: "common language runtime",
        options: [
          "common language runtime",
          "common language ramtype",
          "C language runtime",
          "C ++ language runtime"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "BCL stands for",
        answer: "base class library",
        options: [
          "base class library",
          "basic class library",
          "based classic library",
          "bass class library"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "a root is the storage location containing a referance to a____on the heap",
        answer: "object",
        options: [
          "delegete",
          "class",
          "object",
          "non of the above"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "what is PID stands for",
        answer: "process ID",
        options: [
          "program ID",
          "process ID",
          "pocessor ID",
          "processing ID"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "why kill command is used ?",
        answer: "to terminate a process",
        options: [
          "to start a process",
          "to terminate a process",
          "to make a process",
          "non of the above"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "zombie process is also known as",
        answer: "defunct process",
        options: [
          "child process",
          "parent process",
          "default process",
          "defunct process"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "'$ cut -C' is used for ",
        answer: "cutting columns",
        options: [
          "cut the command",
          "copy the command",
          "cutting columns",
          "cut rows"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "-f suboption in cut command is used for",
        answer: "cutting files",
        options: [
          "cutting forms",
          "cutting files",
          "both A and B",
          "none of the above"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "how many modes are ther in vi editor?",
        answer: "3",
        options: [
          "3",
          "2",
          "4",
          "1"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "",
        answer: "",
        options: [
          "",
          "",
          "",
          ""
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "-dsuboption in tr is used for",
        answer: "deletig character",
        options: [
          "deletig character",
          "detecting characters",
          "default characters",
          "none of the above"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "does tr uses file name as argument ?",
        answer: "yes",
        options: [
          "no",
          "yes",
          "sometimes",
          "none of the above"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "CLI stands for",
        answer: "command line interpreter",
        options: [
          "command line argument",
          "compound line interpreter",
          "command line interpreter",
          "command line interuptor"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "an example for numeric comparision is ",
        answer: "-ne",
        options: [
          "-g",
          "-ne",
          "-z",
          "-n"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "to remove the special meaning of unix meta character,",
        answer: "we use back slash (\) ",
        options: [
          "we use back slash (\) ",
          "we use forward slash (/) ",
          "we use back question mark (?)",
          "none of the above"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "CC stands for ",
        answer: "cloud computing",
        options: [
          "clown computing",
          "cloud calculating",
          "cloud computing",
          "cloud comparing"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "there are ____ types of clients:",
        answer: "3",
        options: [
          "2",
          "3",
          "1",
          "10"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "AJAX stands for",
        answer: "Asynchronous javascript and xml",
        options: [
          "anti javascript file",
          "A javascript and xml",
          "Asynchronous javascript and xml",
          "none of the above"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "expand API",
        answer: "application programming interface",
        options: [
          "amplitude packaging internet",
          "application programming interface",
          "application programming interchange",
          "applicating programming interface"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "the GOGRID API supports one of the following language",
        answer: "java",
        options: [
          "java",
          "java script",
          "c#",
          "unix"
       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "this is not an exaple for popular webservice",
        answer: "kson",
        options: [
          "json",
          "kson",
          "rest",
          "soap"
       ]
    },
    

];    